[
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Dragon Yo-kai 2. Indecisive 3. His favorite phrase is 'Hmmm...'","Answer":"Draaagin"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. White tuxedo 2. Heartful Tribe 3. My darling sweet pea","Answer":"Ray O'Light"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Drizzly drizzle... 2. Dampy damp... 3. Drizzly; drizzly drizzle...","Answer":"Drizzelda"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Holds bells in his right hand 2. A classic Yo-kai 3. Happy happy!","Answer":"High Gnomey"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Neat-freak shogun 2. Loves his antibacterial spray 3. Clean; clean!","Answer":"Washogun"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. First-rate food stall 2. Dashi stock 3. Well den","Answer":"Master Oden"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Holds a small staff in one hand. 2. Loves bread 3. Conjures apparitions","Answer":"Illoo"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Proud of soft skin 2. Puffs up when angry 3. Face pops out of his body","Answer":"Mochismo"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Yo-kai workout leader 2. Peak physical condition 3. Feel the burn!","Answer":"Sergeant Burly"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Eats memories 2. Mysterious Tribe 3. Shaped like a hat","Answer":"Wazzat"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Healthy, thanks to seaweed 2. One of a trio 3. Views Steppa as a rival","Answer":"Wiglin"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Healthy, groovy seaweed 2. One of a trio 3. Views Wiglin as a rival","Answer":"Steppa"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Loved by Wiglin 2. Loved by Steppa 3. Not interested in either","Answer":"Rhyth"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Likes taking detours 2. Worries about scaly sharkskin 3. Vegetarian","Answer":"Chummer"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Green clothes 2. Heartful Tribe 3. Hoards things in bags","Answer":"Ol' Fortune"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Travels atop a cloud 2. Wields a vacuum cleaner 3. Sucks up memories","Answer":"Vacuumory"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Reflective 2. Power of darkness 3. Summons spirits from his mirror","Answer":"Mircle"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Won 2. ...der... 3. ...nyan!","Answer":"Wondernyan"},
{"Category":"YOUKAI","Question":"1. Traditional Japanese clothes 2. Likes big flowers 3. Cherry blossoms","Answer":"Elder Bloom"}
]
